blocktv.com 2019-04-18

# BLOCKTV: Privacy Policy

We, at BLOCKTV are committed to protecting your privacy and your personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). 

We have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we (or others on our behalf) collect from you when you use our Website/Platform/Mobile App (the “Website”) and the services contained within (the “Services“), how is this information collected and how is it used. 

This Privacy Policy is part of and should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions. When you access or use our site, you agree that we (or others on our behalf) may collect, use and disclose your information (including Personal Information) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

##  Collection of Information 

We (or others on our behalf) collect Personal Information from you, including without limitation, your name, credit card information, home or other physical address, email address, phone number and other contact information. We (or others on our behalf) also collect an activity log unique to you that collects certain administrative and traffic information including without limitation source IP address, trades, time of access, date of access, web page(s) visited, language use, software crash reports and type of browser used. We (or others on our behalf) collect the aforesaid information when you visit or use our site, and in your communications with us. 

You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of your Personal Information and all other information you submit to us (or to others on our behalf). 

##  Use of Information 

We use the Personal Information and other information we (or others on our behalf) collect from or about you to deliver the Services, to provide customer support, to process any of your online transactions, meet certain business requirements and for any other purpose related, directly or indirectly, to the operation of the Services. We may disclose your Personal Information (and any other information) to any third parties that provide services to us to allow, enable or improve the provision of the Services to you. Your Personal Information may also be used by us to provide you with promotional offers and information regarding our Services as well as products and services from third parties carefully selected by us, and for us to improve our offering of a range of services and improved customer service. We may also use the aforesaid information to track your use of our site and for other internal purposes, such as evaluating, providing, and improving our services and our site. 

We may disclose your Personal Information and other information we collect (or others on our behalf) from or about you if required to do so by law, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process, or to protect and defend our rights or property, the personal safety of users of the Services or the public. We reserve the right to share the aforesaid information with banks, credit card companies, and appropriate agencies, if we determine in our sole discretion that you have cheated or attempted to defraud us, or if we suspect you of committing any fraudulent activity (including of fraudulent payment), or any other prohibited transaction. 

We may use your Personal Information internally for our general commercial purposes including, among other things, to offer our own, our affiliates’ or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest, but only us, our subsidiaries and contractors involved in distributing the offers or providing the products or services will have access to your Personal Information. Our subsidiaries and contractors will be required to use any Personal Information we provide them only for that intended purpose. 

##  International Transfers 

We may transfer any information (including Personal Information) outside your country of residence and outside the European Union (where applicable) and store it in other countries; the data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as comprehensive as those in your country of residence or the European Union (where applicable) – in these instances we will take steps to ensure that a similar level of protection is given to your Personal Information. 

##  Disclosing Your Information: 

We may reveal Personal Information about you to unaffiliated third parties: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) to allow them to market to you. We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-Personal Information, such as usage statistics of our Products, to our affiliates and third parties. 

##  Choice / Opt-Out 

By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you hereby allow us to provide you with communications from us, as well as from third parties, either relating to the Services or relating to other (including, but not limited to, commercial) matters and offers. You hereby acknowledge and consent to the sending of such communications, and will not argue that such activity amounts to sending of unsolicited communications, you also hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for the communication sent to you by third parties, their content and method of distribution. 

##  Cookies 

We (or others on our behalf) use a browser feature known as cookies, which are small text files which are placed on your computer or equipment to track your activities, record your preferences, and make our site more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are used by us to help track your clicks and pass information as you go through the pages within our site. Cookies can allow us to associate navigational information from browsing visits with Personal Information you provide at our site. 

The cookies we may use include:   
a) Session cookies: These temporary cookies expire and are automatically erased whenever you close your browser window. We use session cookies to grant our users access to content and to enable actions they must be logged in to do.   
b) Persistent cookies: These usually have an expiration date in the distant future and remain in your browser until they expire, or you manually delete them. We use persistent cookies to better understand usage patterns, so we can improve the site for our customers. For example, we may use a persistent cookie to associate you with your user account or to remember that your choices, but this only works when cookies on the Website are enabled.   
c) Third party cookies: We permit limited third parties to place cookies to provide us with better insights into the use of the Services or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our website. 

We may also permit third party service providers to place cookies, as indicated above, to perform analytic or marketing functions where you are notified of them and you have consented to the usage. We do not control the use of such third party cookies or the resulting information and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. 

Your use of the Website will be deemed to be your consent to the placement of cookies on your computer or other device. If you prefer not to receive cookies through the Website, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow only “trusted” websites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Website and use it. 

If you refuse cookies, this will limit system performance and may even cause certain features of the Website to malfunction or not to work at all. 

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from the Website, if your computer supports such capabilities. In an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers, we also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies. 

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

##  Security 

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the Personal Information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. We are not able to guarantee that the safeguards implemented and that the Services will not be subject to malfunction, guarantee that there will not be any unlawful interception or unauthorized access to the Personal Information, nor can we guarantee that your private communications in respect of the Services will remain private. 

All our employees and data processors that have access to and are associated with the processing of your Personal Information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your information. 

##  Links to Other Sites 

Our site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites, and any information collected by these third-party online sites is not governed by this Privacy Policy, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the policies (including privacy policies), practices, actions or omissions of such third parties. 

##  Special Circumstances 

If we sell, assign or transfer some or all of our business or assets to a successor or acquirer, or if we are acquired by or merge with a third party, or if we file for bankruptcy or become insolvent, we may sell, assign or transfer all your Personal Information and other information provided by you or about you, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer. 

##  Disclaimer 

The Services operate “AS-IS” and “AS-AVAILABLE”, without liability of any kind. We cannot guarantee, nor do we represent that there will be error-free performance and will provide complete and absolute security regarding the privacy of your Personal Information, and we will not be liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to the use or release of Personal Information. 

##  Your Acceptance of this Policy 

By agreeing to our Terms and Conditions during the registration process on our site, or by continued use of our Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, and to any changes we may make to this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the changes on our site. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly so as to be kept apprised of any such changes. Your continued use of our Services following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept these changes. 

If you reside in the European Union, you have the right under the General Data Protection Regulation to request from us access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data, data portability, restriction of processing of your personal data, the right to object to processing of your personal data, and the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. 

To request access to or rectification, portability or erasure of your personal data, or to delete your account, visit [newsdesk@blocktv.com](mailto:newsdesk@blocktv.com).
